The thing about the station is that we're used to involving Congolese youth, most of whom want to go live in danger.
On the contrary, most are looking for opportunities, looking for a better life.
And most just want to succeed in their lives.
So they want an environment that guarantees them that better, dream life.
I, generally, have already faced prejudice when I was in high school.
They called me Ikeike, which means "we didn't care" and all that.
People told me I shouldn't become who I am, that I'm really short, like your height.
Because I had a tiny head, I was short in stature and all that.
So over time, I'm not the same size I used to be.
And I kept the small head, but maybe today there's a lot of knowledge,
direct skills that I can even pass on, and that let me assert myself in society.